不 没关系 我一般也起来了
No, no, it's cool. I'm usually up.
我以前整整七年
I used to open for a coffee shop
都给咖啡店开门
every day for seven years.
大脑会保留一些你不需要的习惯
Your brain, it gets wired to things you don't need anymore.
我还喜欢随身带着手机
I still like carrying around my cell phone, too.
以后它会响铃
One of these days it's gonna ring
然后吓我一大跳
and freak my ass out.
如果你碰巧打到野猪 能分我一条腿吗？
Hey, if you happen to bag a boar out there, can I have a leg?
来做意大利熏火腿
To make a prosciutto.
灾变前我就在地下室熏肉了
I used to cure meats in my basement even before all this.
我做的泡菜也超好吃
I made some kick-ass pickles, too.
行 奥利维亚
Sure, Olivia.
谢谢
Thanks.
来杀了我吧
Come and get me.
《行尸走肉》
我没看见 但它就在附近
I don't see it, but it's close.
只有一只
There's just one of them.
我们不会久留的
We won't be here long.
你怎么看？
So what do you think?
等里面没人了我们就进去
We can go in when it's empty.
怎么做？晚上那里会锁门
How is that? It's locked up at night.
走窗户 只有个插销 我可以拉开
The window. There's just a latch. I can leave it open.
- 插销？- 是啊
- A latch? - Yeah.
万一某个蠢货扣上了呢？
What if one of those pricks shuts it?
那就等几天 再拉开插销
Wait a couple of days, leave it open again.
它越来越近了
It's getting closer.
我们越早做越好
We need to do it sooner than later.
现在他们没监视我们
Right now, they're not watching us.
还没担心这种会面
Not worrying about meetings like this.
我们也许需要枪 也许不需要
We may need the guns, we may not.
不管怎么样 我们都需要
We will whatever way it goes.
他们是我见过的最幸运的人
They're the luckiest damn people I ever met.
而他们越来越幸运了
And they just keep getting luckier.
怎讲？
How's that?
我们现在来了
We're here now.
他们有几个小箱子
They've got a couple of footlockers
里面都是9毫米自动枪
just full of 9 millimeter autos,
鲁格手枪 卡尔特克步枪
Rugers, Kel-Tecs.
就扔在里面 他们不用那些枪
Just tossed in there. They don't use them.
永远也不会知道不见了
They're never gonna know they're gone.
有人已经拿了一把 对吧？
Someone's got one now, right?
听着 其他人 让他们努力融合
Listen, the others, we want them to try.
你也是
You, too.
所以不要声张 我们三个知道就行
So we keep it quiet. Just us.
它来了
Here it comes.
- 我来 - 等等
- I got him. - Hey, wait.
我们说的是带我出来练枪
We said we were taking me out shooting.
回去时弹夹可不能是满的
I couldn't go back with a full mag.
真幸运 它来了
Lucky he came by.
我们该回去了
We should get back.
你拉开插销 我们伺机行动
You'll pull the latch, we'll pick our moment.
我们没必要靠运气
Us, we don't need to be lucky.
那是什么
What the hell's that?
是个W吗？
Is that a W?
是啊
Yeah.
我不知道这是不是什么把戏
I don't know if this is some kind of play,
把权力交给陌生人
handing authority to strangers.
制止打架斗殴的权力
The authority to break up fistfights.
如果真是那样 她也该给达里尔一套警服
If it was just that, she should have given one of these to Daryl.
我不知道这是为了我们还是他们
I don't know if it's for us or for them.
也许迪安娜真想除掉我们
Or maybe Deanna's trying to get rid of us and them.
但是让我俩穿上警服
You put these jackets on me and you,
让人们都看到
have the people see it.
如果这是把戏 那真聪明
If that's the play, that'd be smart.
她看起来挺聪明
And she seems smart.
那时聪明还是现在聪明？
Smart for then or smart for now?
这就是现在
This is now.
出来
Come out!
快点
Now!
你凭声音就能分辨行尸和人类吗？
You can tell the difference between walkers and humans by sound?
你能分辨好人和坏人吗？
Can you tell the difference between a good guy and a bad guy?
瑞克好像不怎么擅长
Rick doesn't seem to be an expert at that.
现在没什么区别了
There ain't much of a difference no more.
这就是你对你同伴的看法吗？
That how you feel about your people?
你为什么跟踪我？
Why you following me?
我不知道你也在
I didn't know I was.
我只是出来打兔子的
I came out to hunt rabbits.
我知道你为什么出来
I know why you're out here.
介意我加入吗？
Mind if I join?
跟上
Keep up.
保持安静
And keep quiet.
你保护人民 服务大众
You protect and serve.
巡逻 沿墙警戒 照看孩童
You patrol, walk the wall, watch out for the kids.
假如出现了冲突 你就去解决
If there's a conflict, you solve it.
大家会听你的
And people will listen to you.
因为我们穿着防风衣吗？
Because we're wearing windbreakers?
因为他们相信这身制服
Because they believe in this.
因为我要求他们这样做
Because I'm telling them to.
这里曾经住了个警官
A police officer used to live here.
所以我们有这些警服
So we had these jackets
而且我希望弄得正式一点
and I wanted to make it official.
这样才有权威
So it's official.
总有一天这里会有政府的
There's gonna be a government here one day.
那也是为什么我希望玛姬来协助我
That's why I want Maggie working with me.
将来还会有一个警队
There's gonna be a police force.
所以我希望你俩起个头
That's why I want you two to start it.
我看到了一个生机勃勃的社区
I see a vibrant community here
有工业 有商业
with industry, commerce,
有文明
civilization.
真正的生活
Real lives.
有可能只是很原始的生活 但是？
It might be horses and mills, but...
怎么了？
What?
听上去像是异想天开吗？
Does that sound like pie in the sky?
不
No.
我们能谈谈安保工作吗？
Can we talk security?
我们需要墙边一直有人巡逻
We need a constant patrol along the walls.
不仅仅是查看哪里有缺口
Not just looking for damage,
还要警戒是否有人爬进来
but signs that anyone climbed in from outside.
你可以顺着支柱爬上来
You can move right up the supports.
我就会那样做
That's what I'd do.
如今人类才是真正的威胁
People are the real threat now.
瑞克 我知道你觉得
Rick, I know you think
墙内人人都应该武装起来
that we should all be armed within the walls.
我不能那样做
I can't do that.
没关系
That's fine.
你照我说的做
You make these changes,
就不用武装了
we won't need to.
打扰了
Excuse me.
我申请在钟塔上放哨
I want to volunteer to be one of the lookouts in the clock tower.
钟塔上没人放哨
There are no lookouts in the clock tower.
- 什么？- 之前我们看见上面有人
- What? - We saw someone up there earlier.
那是我儿子斯宾塞放上去的空膛步枪
That was an empty rifle my son Spencer put up there.
他有时会上去 但不经常
He mans it sometimes, but not often.
听着 没有放哨的必要
Look, there hasn't been the need.
我们需要立刻在塔上设哨 时刻戒备
We need a lookout in that tower right now, 24/7.
只有这样才能提前发现敌情
It's the only way we'll be able to see if someone's coming at us.
好吧 我们轮班放哨
Okay, okay, we'll make shifts.
我会尽可能多轮几班
I'll take those shifts, as many as possible.
为什么？
Why?
萨沙是我们最好的射手之一
Sasha's one of our best shots.
她可以的
She can do it.
今天我会让斯宾塞上去
I'm gonna put Spencer up there today.
我会考虑让你成为我们的主要哨兵
I'll consider you being our primary lookout,
但我想要一点回报
but I want something in return.
今晚 我在我家为你们所有人
Tonight I'm hosting a welcome
举办了一个欢迎会
for all of you at my home.
我希望你能到场
I want you to be there.
为什么？
Why?
今晚过来 然后我们再谈
Come tonight. Then we'll talk about it.
青豆泥
Mashed lima beans,
可可粉 再加一点甜味剂
cocoa powder, a little sweetener.
灾变前我也会吃的 我发誓
I would have eaten it before all this, I swear.
它含蛋白质 能填饱肚子
It's protein and it fills you up.
听起来真可口
Sounds delicious.
我等下回来 我得去求瑞克
I'll be back. I've got to go beg Rick
今晚帮帮忙
for some help with tonight.
假如你还需要其他什么就告诉我 姐妹
You need anything else, you hit me, girl.
好的 谢啦
Okay, thanks.
你听说了派对的事吗？
You've heard about the party?
人人都会到场
Everyone's gonna be there.
没错
That's right.
那就今晚行动
So tonight, then.
应该可以溜出去
Should be able to slip out.
武器库就在迪安娜家旁边
The armory is right next to Deanna's.
我会支援你的
I'll back you up.
大家可能会好奇新治安官或者卡尔的爸爸
People might wonder where their new constable is
去哪了
or Carl's dad.
好吧
Okay.
我们不能用达里尔
We can't use Daryl.
大家在盯着他的一举一动
They're watching every move he makes.
没关系
It's fine.
你知道这里好在哪里吗？
You know what's great about this place?
我又能变成隐形人了
I get to be invisible again.
我想抓住它已经好几个月了
I've been trying to catch him for months,
想把它带回去
bring him inside.
它叫巴顿斯
His name is Buttons.
有一个孩子以前看到它从门口跑过
One of the kids saw him run by the gate a while back.
觉得它应该叫巴顿斯
Thought he looked like a Buttons.
我已经好久没看到它了
I haven't seen him for a while.
我还担心它死了呢
I was afraid it was too late.
每次埃里克和我靠近它 就会吓着它
Every time Eric or I come close, he gets spooked.
你以前套过马吗？
Have you done this before?
我们那伙儿人套过
My group did.
但是它们没在外面待那么久
But they weren't out there that long.
在外面待得越久就越野性
The longer they're out there, the more they become what they really are.
我不会伤害你的
I ain't gonna hurt ya.
好吗？
All right?
过来 孩子
Come on, boy.
好的
Yeah.
继续吃吧
Just keep on eating.
好的
Yeah.
好孩子
Good boy.
你以前也是有主人的 对吧？
Yeah, you used to be somebody's, huh?
现在你是自己的主人
Now you're just yours.
该死
Shit!
快点 它们来了
Come on, they're coming!
走吧
Come on.
你真的用苹果酱替代鸡蛋吗？
You really substitute applesauce for eggs?
真是毁我三观了
That could change my life.
这事儿只有你知我知
If we can keep that between you and me.
这是这些饼干的秘方
It's sort of the secret to these cookies.
你说真的吗？
Are you serious?
是的
I am.
女生总得有些秘密呀
A girl's got only so many secrets.
我会守口如瓶的
It'll die with me.
巧克力比较紧缺
Uh, the chocolate is kind of a trick.
你真的有巧克力吗？
You actually have it?
我只能给你一小块
I can only ration you a quarter bar.
足够用了
I'll make it work.
奥利维亚
Hey, Olivia.
我们来取枪
We're gonna need to make a withdrawal.
这么晚啊？
Late start?
女老板让我在派对开始前
Boss lady wants me to check
检查一下东墙的支杆
that strut on the east wall before the party.
去后面拿吧
Head on back.
卡萝尔 需要什么随便拿
Carol, just grab what you need.
- 巧克力在大厅的冰柜里 - 好的
- Chocolate's in the hall freezer. - Okay.
你怕枪吗 女士？
You afraid of guns, ma'am?
不怕 我…
No, I...
我在外面的时候有一把手枪
Well, I had a handgun and I carried a rifle
和一支步枪 但是我不太会用
when we were on the outside, but I'm not an expert.
至少不会用那种枪
Not with those, at least.
我叫托宾
Well, my name is Tobin.
你想学的话 我可以教你
And whenever you want, i'd be happy to teach you.
以防万一嘛
Just better to be safe than sorry.
那真好 谢了 托宾
That'd be nice. Thanks, Tobin.
谢谢 奥利维亚
Thank you, Olivia.
你会骑马吗？
You ride horses?
我会骑车
I ride bikes.
我猜你说的不是自行车
I take it you don't mean 10-speeds.
我知道你觉得自己是外人
I know you're feeling like an outsider.
这不是你的错
It's not your fault, you know.
埃里克和我
Eric and I,
人们很多时候依然把我们看成外人
we're still looked at as outsiders in a lot of ways.
我们听过很多正派的人…
We've heard our fair share of well-meaning,but ...
对我们开一些没有恶意
hilariously offensive things
但非常难听的玩笑
from some otherwise really nice men and women.
这是人的本性
People are people.
越是害怕 越是愚蠢
The more afraid they get, the more stupid they get.
恐惧会让智商降低
Fear shrinks the brain.
他们因为不同的理由害怕你和我
They're scared of you and me for different reasons.
因为认识我 所以他们不那么怕我
They're less scared of me because they know me.
日复一日渐渐不怕了
It's less and less every day.
所以…
So...
让他们认识认识你
let them get to know you.
你今晚应该去参加迪安娜的派对
You should go to Deanna's party tonight.
我没什么可证明的
I got nothing to prove.
我在外面遇到过很多坏人
I met a lot of bad people out here
他们干了很多坏事
doing a lot of bad shit.
人们什么都不怕
They weren't afraid of nothing.
他们怕
Yeah, they were.
天啊
Oh, my.
欢迎
Welcome.
你们能来太好了
Oh, it's so good to see you.
卡尔 感谢你们能来
Hi, Carl. Thank you for coming.
你知道 我还没面试她呢
You know, I didn't get a chance to interview this one.
我羡慕她
I envy her.
为什么？
Why?
她有机会见证这地方的未来
She'll get to see what this place will become.
来吧 进来
Come. Come on in.
我不太习惯这种场合
I don't know about this.
他们有啤酒
They have beer.
那我试试
I'm gonna try.
你是瑞克
You're Rick.
瑞克 这是我丈夫雷吉
Rick, this is my husband Reg.
你是个很出色的人
You're a pretty remarkable guy.
这话怎么说？
Well, how's that?
我看了录像带 所有人的
I watched the tapes. All of them.
大家对你的评价
The things those people said about you.
你为他们做过的事
The things you did for them.
外面的墙不是你建的吗？
Didn't you build that wall out there?
对 是我 有人帮我
Yeah, I did, with help.
很多人帮我 虽说是个不可思议的成就
A lot of it. And it's a damned incredible achievement.
但是 也不过是面墙而已
But it's a wall.
十四个人 在这种世界？
14 lives in this world?
我觉得你比我厉害
I think you have me beat.
我们现在都受到墙的保护 所以…
Well, we're standing behind that wall right now, dear. So...
你俩是平手
let's call it a tie.
我很高兴你能加入
Well, I'm glad you're here.
现在 喝一杯吧
Now, take a glass.
不用了
I'm good.
你不用绷着
You don't have to be.
这就对了
There you go.
喝吧
Go on.
很好 欢迎
Right. Welcome.
谢谢
Thank you.
得快点了
Gotta move quick.
它被包围了
He's pinned in with them.
我去对付远处的
I got the far ones.
谢谢
Thanks.
我对付右边的
I got the ones on the right.
干吧
Go ahead.
它总在跑
He always ran.
你尽过力了
You were trying to help him.
你还好吗？
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
只是不太适应这个场合
Just isn't really my thing.
- 我还是走吧 - 别走
- I think I'm gonna head out. - No, no.
你不能逃
You're not bailing.
大家一起受罪呢 伙计
We're in this together, man.
你现在跟我们在一起
You're here with us now.
跟家人在一起
You're here with family.
来吧
Come on.
达里尔
Daryl.
我以为你去了那边的派对
Thought you were going to that party over there.
我压根没打算去
Oh, I was never going to go
因为埃里克脚踝受伤了 感谢上帝
Because of Eric's ankle, thank God.
那你为什么让我去？
Why the hell did you tell me to go, then?
我说让你试试 你试了
I said try. You did.
有这个心本身就很重要
It's a thought that counts thing.
- 好吧 - 进来吧
- All right. - Hey, come in.
吃点晚饭
Have some dinner.
来吧 老兄
Come on, man.
有很正宗的意粉
It's some pretty serious spaghetti.
瞧 她来了 说明武器库没人了
Look, she's here, which means it's empty, so...
我和你一起去
I'll go with you.
不 记住…
No, remember...
你是隐形人
You're invisible.
瑞克 这是我丈夫皮特
Hey, Rick, this is my husband Pete.
很高兴见到你
Good to meet you.
感谢你担任我们的治安官
I wanted to thank you for taking on being our constable.
如果社区照此速度发展下去
If we keep growing at this rate,
可能还需要更多的治安官
we're gonna need even more.
希望如此
I hope so.
下周来我办公室一趟吧？
You want to come by my office next week?
我为你做个检查
I'll take a look at you.
也许我应该事先讲明自己是个医生
And I probably should have said I was a doctor first.
先说后说都挺体贴的
I think it sounded nice either way.
我去给我们续杯
I'm going to get us a refill.
- 我去吧 - 我说了我去
- Oh, I can do it. - I'm on it.
开心吗？
Having fun?
挺开心的
Yes, I am.
这问题挺蠢的 对吧？
That's kind of a stupid question, right?
不
No.
但是 这里看上去挺不错的
Still, this place has a pretty amazing view.
是吗？
Yeah?
是啊 你看
Yeah, take a look.
像以前一样的平凡生活
Ordinary life like before.
和以前也不大一样
Well, not like before.
是啊
No.
没错 不一样了
Yeah, no.
我想说的是… 至少更好了
I mean... I mean, it's better.
不是说外面 而是这里
Not out there, in here.
每个人都经历过苦痛
You know, everyone's been through it somehow.
每个人都是
Everyone.
很多好东西消失了
And a lot of things disappeared.
但是很多糟粕也消失了
But a lot of bullshit went with it.
他们都有其截然不同的背景
They're all from totally different backgrounds,
来自不同的地方
different places.
本来此生不会相见 然而…
They never would have even met. And ...
现在他们却是彼此生活的一部分
now they're part of each other's lives.
他们就是彼此的生活
They are each other's lives.
我只是想说 人人都会失去一些东西
I'm just saying, we all lost things,
但有失必有得
but we got something back.
虽然那还不够
It isn't enough,
但至少有所得
but it's something.
不 是平手 老兄
No, it was a tie, man.
你也看到了 对吧？
You saw it, right?
你说的没错 确实挺不错的
Yeah, yeah, it's a pretty good view.
- 妈 - 什么事
- Mom. - Yeah.
没饼干了
There's no more cookies.
我刚好认识做饼干的人
Well, I happen to know the cookie maker.
她是我的好友
She's a good friend of mine.
或许我可以去让她
And I might be able to see about her
为你做一整炉的饼干
making a whole batch just for you.
妈 他手上没盖章
Mom, he doesn't have a stamp.
你想盖个章吗？
Do you want a stamp?
当然
Sure.
看见了没？你已经正式成为我们的一员了
See? Now you're officially one of us.
是啊
Yeah.
山姆
Hey, Sam.
山姆 等等 别乱跑
Sam, wait, don't run.
- 我们待会见 - 好
- I'll see you later. - Yeah.
你想逃走是吧？
Trying to make a getaway, huh?
我可以装作没开门
I can pretend I didn't make it.
我是萨沙
I'm Sasha.
我是斯宾塞 迪安娜是我的母亲
I'm Spencer. Deanna's my mom.
你母亲…
Your mom...
她看上去人很好
she seems nice.
如果你跟我待在一起
Well, if you want to hang with me,
我可以确保你不被尼德迈尔夫人缠住
I'll make sure you don't get stuck with Mrs. Neudermyer.
她真的特别喜欢
She really, really likes
跟别人讲自己多想要一个面条机
talking about how much she wants a pasta maker.
你绝对不想聊那个
It's not a conversation you want to have.
失陪了
Excuse me.
谢谢
Thanks.
你出去的时候
Mmm, when you're out there,
如果你恰好在商店里
if you happen to be in a store or something,
尼德迈尔夫人很想要一台面条机
Mrs. Neudermyer is really looking for a pasta maker.
我们都不想再听她念叨这事了
And we're all really trying to get her to shut up about it.
我们这有好几箱干意面
I mean, we have crates of dried pasta in here,
但她非要自己做
but she wants to make her own or something.
我觉得她只是想找点话头吧 所以…
I really think she just wants something to talk about, so...
如果你出去时有看到
if you see one out on your travels,
那真是帮了我们一个大忙…
it would go a long way to...
我以为你们谈过了
I thought it was done.
你还没问他吗？
You didn't ask him already?
问我什么？
Ask me what?
我得到这所房子时 这里有车架
When I got the place, there was that frame
还有些零件和设备
and some parts and equipment.
以前住这里的人造的
Whoever lived here built them.
这些零件也太多了
It's a lot of parts for one bike.
我每次出去看到什么零件 都会带回来
Whenever I came across any parts out there, I brought them back.
我不知道该拿什么零件
I didn't know what I'd need.
我总以为我能学会怎么做 但是
I always thought I'd learn how to do it, but
我觉得你知道该怎么做
I get the feeling you already know what to do with it.
重点是
And the thing is,
你需要一辆摩托
you're going to need a bike.
为什么？
Why?
我告诉迪安娜别给你安排工作
I told Deanna not to give you a job
因为我已为你准备了一份
because I think I have one for you.
我希望你成为亚历山大的另一位招募员
I'd like you to be Alexandria's other recruiter.
我不想再让埃里克冒生命危险了
I don't want Eric risking his life anymore.
你想让我冒生命危险 对吗？
You want me risking mine, right?
对 因为你做事有分寸
Yeah, because you know what you're doing.
你在外面很厉害
You're good out there.
但你不属于外面
But you don't belong out there.
我知道让人们了解你很难
I know it's hard getting used to people getting used to you.
我也理解你需要偶尔出去一趟
And I understand right now you need to be out there sometimes.
我也是
So do I.
但我希望你帮我招募的主要原因是
But the main reason why I want you to help me recruit
你能分辨出好人和坏人
is because you do know the difference between a good person and a bad person.
反正我也没别的事可做
I got nothing else to do.
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
Yeah.
我帮你打几只兔子
I'll get you some rabbits.
太好了
Great.
你换刀了吗？
You packing different steel nowadays?
对
Yeah.
以刀为生 为刀而死…
Live by it, you die by it...
又用刀吃土豆泡芙
and eat potato puffs by it.
祈求上帝你不必再用它了
Pray to God you don't have to use it again.
祈求上帝你不会适应不再用它
Pray to God you don't get used to not using it again.
刀就在你背上…
It's on your back...
即便已经卸下来了
even when it's off your back.
你到底喝了多少？
How much have you had to drink?
我是大块头
I am a large man.
自然喝的啤酒也多
And I have had many beers to make up for that.
你知道吗？
And you know what?
通过我的勇敢搭讪…
By that brave act, I have...
我逐渐发现
I have come to realize that things
我已经适应现在这样了
have worked out pretty damn well for me.
那你呢？
How about you?
你做出了什么努力？
What have you done?
我穿上了这条裙子
I put on this dress.
再努力一点
Try again.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
山姆 你在这里做什么？
Sam, what are you doing here?
我跟着你来的
I followed you.
本来指望你会再做一些饼干
I was hoping you were going to make more cookies,
但你却来了这里
but then you came here.
我可以再做一些
Well, I could make more.
我可以为你做一整炉
I could make a whole batch just for you.
- 你喜欢吗？- 当然
- Would you like that? - Yes.
- 我是说 请做一些吧 - 好
- I mean, yes, please. - Okay.
但你得答应我
But you've got to promise me
不告诉别人我来过这里
you can keep it secret that I came here.
但我得告诉我妈
But I'd have to tell my mom.
我什么事都告诉我妈
I mean, I tell my mom everything.
你不能告诉任何人
You can never tell anyone,
特别是你妈
especially your mom.
因为如果你告诉她…
Because if you do...
某天早上 你醒来后…
one morning you'll wake up...
会发现自己不在床上
and you won't be in your bed.
那我在哪里？
Where will I be?
你会在墙外
You'll be outside the walls
很远很远的地方
far, far away
被捆在树上
tied to a tree.
你会不停尖叫
And you'll scream and scream
因为你很害怕
because you'll be so afraid.
没人会来救你
No one will come to help
因为没人能听见你
because no one will hear you.
但是 有些东西能听见你
Well, something will hear you.
怪物会来抓你
The monsters will come.
外面的那些
The ones out there.
它们来抓你时 你跑也跑不掉
And you won't be able to run away when they come for you.
它们会撕碎你
And they will tear you apart
生吞活剥你
and eat you up all while you're still alive.
疼得撕心裂肺
All while you can still feel it.
之后
And then afterwards,
没人知道你怎么了
no one will ever know what happened to you.
或者 你可以保证
Or you can promise
永远不告诉别人你看到了什么
not to ever tell anyone what you saw here
一切就不会发生了
and then nothing will happen.
你还能得到饼干
And you'll get cookies.
很多饼干
Lots of cookies.
我觉得你知道该怎么做了
I know what I think you should do.
景色也挺不错的 对吗？
That's a pretty good view, too, isn't it?
我很久没抱过宝宝了
It's been a long time since I held one of these.
她和卡尔…
She and Carl...
是我留下的原因
they're why I'm still here.
我知道你想对我说什么
And I get what you've been telling me.
是什么？
What's that?
这里没那么糟
Here isn't that bad.
你想抱她吗？
Do you want to take her?
好
Yeah.
萨沙 加入我们吧
Sasha. Come join us.
我保证你只用听就行
I promise all you have to do is listen.
来吧
Come on.
好吧
Okay.
保佑她 我不知道她为什么看那么久
Bless her heart. I don't get what takes her so long.
我们只有一本书
I mean, we only have one copy
读书会的目的不就是让大家都能看上吗
and the point of book club is that we all read the book.
我真希望能有牙医来我家
I just keep hoping that a dentist shows up at our gates.
- 他牙不好 - 我是说
- It's his teeth. - I mean,
新鲜的时候好吃多了
it's just so much better when it's fresh.
I mean, it's just so much better when it's fresh.
萨沙 亲爱的 你爱吃什么菜？
Sasha, honey, what's your favorite meal?
我想以后给你做
I'd love to cook it for you sometime.
我为每位新人都做
I'm doing it for all the new arrivals.
- 我不知道 - 你当然知道
- I don't know. - Of course you do.
每个人都有爱吃的菜 你的是什么？
Everyone has favorites. So what's yours?
想吃什么都行
Whatever you want.
我只是担心
I'm just worried that I'll
做了你不爱吃的菜 你懂吗？
end up cooking something you hate, you know?
你担心吗？
You're worried?
你担心的就是这个吗？
That's what you worry about?!
我在努力弄明白是怎么回事
I'm trying to figure out what it is.
到底是怎么回事
What it is exactly.
这一切…
This...
不是真的
it isn't real.
萨沙 你经历了很多
Sasha, you've been through a lot
这点我明白 但是你刚说的话…
and I accept that, but what you just said...
是胡话
that's bullshit.
选吧
Take your pick.
听着 我想了想
Look, I've been thinking.
我们真的需要枪吗？
Do we really need these?
如果事情变糟了 当然
I mean, things go bad, yeah, sure.
我们该做什么做什么 但是如你所说
We do what we gotta do, but it's like you said.
不需要枪也能解决
We don't need these for that.
目前不需要
Right now we don't.
你不是想让我试试吗？
You wanted me to try, right?
我不要了
I'm good.
瑞克
Hey, Rick.